

## **CONTACT**

Tel: +253 77 48 47 07

E-MAIL:

ashrafmohamedaa253@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVES**

Full-stack Web Developer with 4 years of experience in both frontend and backend, primarily using JavaScript. I am seeking a position where I can continue to grow my skills and be a part of a team that will benefit from my relentless effort.

# ASHRAF MOHAMED ADEN

# MSc in Information Systems Full stack developer

### **EDUCATION**

KOBE INSTITUTE OF COMPUTING, KOBE JAPAN

Sep 2019

MASTERS IN INFORMATION SYSTEMS SCIENCES

**DRTP, DAKAR SENEGAL** 

June 2016 CCNA R&S

**ESTM, DAKAR SENEGAL** 

Oct 2014

**BACHELOR NETWORKS AND TELECOMMUNICATIONS** 

# **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Aug 2021 – Present Tedagua Djibouti

Scada operator

Jan 2020 – Present Freelance web development

Jul 2020 – Dec. 2020 LA POSTE DE DJIBOUTI, DJIBOUTI

Software developer

- Designing and implementing new management systems
- Developing front end architecture.
- Designing user interactions on web pages.
- Developing back-end website applications.
- Ensuring responsiveness of applications.
- Designing and developing APIs.

# Sep 2019 – Jun 2020 Government Administration, Software developer

- Designing and developing APIs.
- Working with others departments and fixing existing applications bugs
- Upgrading user interfaces
- Creating and Designing databases
- Testing and evaluating new programs
- Maintaining and upgrading existing systems
- Training users

# Aug 2018 – Aug 2018 UNICLE.CO, OSAKA JAPAN Stage

- JICA ABE Initiative program, 2 weeks Internship
- Learn and study Japanese work environment
- Practice business Japanese language for 2 weeks

### SKILLS AND TECH STACK

# EXPERIENCE

- HTML / CSS / JavaScript
- Angular / Vue.js / Nuxt.js / Node.js
- Java / Spring Boot / Hibernate
- MySQL/NoSQL/MONGODB
- Bootstrap/SASS

- Knowledge of Linux and scripting language (Bash, Python)
- Proficiency with various development, testing and deployment tools (Git, Jenkins, Docker, Kubernetes, Ansible)
- Experience in developing CI/CD pipelines using Jenkins/Git Actions
- Experience in building and deploying Docker containers

#### **CERTIFICATION**

• AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate on April 2nd, 2022.